Guide to the Records of the 7th Regiment 1767-1983 (bulk 1830-1947) MS 556
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI: Recreational Activities, 1873-1950, 12416
  - Subseries 1: Rifle Club, 1879-1947, 12426
    - Queen's Westminsters Match, New York, 1906; 12436 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Queen's Westminsters Matches, [1905, 1906]; 12435 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Other Material, 1882-1903; 12434 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Record Book--Rifle Practice, 1873-1874; 12433 (Volume 373)
    - Rifle Club/Practice--Programs, Manuals, 1873-1908; 12432 (Volume 374)
    - Minute Book, 1892; 12431 (Volume 375)
    - Rifle Records, 1896-1907; 12430 (Volume 376)
    - Score Book, 1905, 1906; 12429 (Volume 377)
    - Scrapbook--Queen's Westminsters Match, England, 1905; 12428 (Volume 378)
    - Scrapbook--Queen's Westminsters Match, 1906; 12427 (Volume 379)
  - Subseries 2: Athletics, 1884-1950, 12417
    Athletics material primarily consists of programs for the annual 7th Regiment Games. Also included are Athletic Association minutes and various programs, schedules and flyers relating to baseball, tennis, golf, and lacrosse events.
    - Programs--Annual Games, [1891]-1907; 12425 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Programs--Annual Games, 1911-1925; 12424 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Programs--Annual Games, 1946-1950; 12423 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Various Sports, 1892-1950; 12422 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Programs--Games (boxed together), 1884-1912; 12421 (Volume 380)
    - Minute Book--Athletic Association, 1894-1897; 12420 (Volume 381)
    - Minute Book--Athletic Association, 1897-1902; 12419 (Volume 382)
    - Minute Book--Athletic Association, 1902-1904; 12418 (Volume 383)
- Series XII: Library, 1860-1940, 12408
  The material in this series relate to the administration and collection of the 7th Regiment library. This includes catalog cards and lists of books and materials in the library.
  - Certificates from Libraries Stating Receipt of History of the Seventh Regiment, 1860, 1870; 12415 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - List of Books Transferred from 7th Regiment Library to the Haye Foundation Library, 1932; 12414 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Cards from the Card Catalog of the 7th Regiment Library, Undated; 12413 (Box 43)
  - Cards from the Card Catalog of the 7th Regiment Library, Undated; 12412 (Box 44)
  - Cards from the Card Catalog of the 7th Regiment Library, Undated; 12411 (Box 45)
  - Books Loaned, 1903 Oct.; 12410 (Volume 384)
  - Inventory of Items in Library, 1885-1940; 12409 (Volume 385)
- Series XIII: Publications, 1811-1976, 12269
  The publications series contains 7th Regiment and non-7th Regiment publications from the 7th Regiment Library.
  - Subseries 1: 7th Regiment Publications, 12314
    This subseries contains the publications and material regarding the business and printing of the publications of the 7th Regiment. The main publications of the 7th include the Seventh Regiment Gazette and the Seventh Regiment Guardsman. Most of the material in this subseries is either copies of the Seventh Regiment Gazette or publication material regarding the Gazette. Other publications include the Seventh Regiment Field Gazette, the Camp Worth Journal, and the Merritt Dispatch. The series also includes the mock-ups, photos, article submissions, and any correspondence having to do with publications. Newsletters for specific companies are located in Series II.
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1895 Oct. 1-1887 June 1; 12407 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1887 Aug. 1-1887 Dec. 1; 12406 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1891 Aug.-1891 Nov.; 12405 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1892 Mar.-1892 Nov.; 12404 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1895 Feb., 1896 Dec.; 12403 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1897 Jan.-1897 Nov.; 12402 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1898 Jan.-1898 July; 12401 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1889 Aug.-1898 Dec.; 12400 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1899 Jan.-1899 June; 12399 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1899 July-1899 Dec.; 12398 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1900 Jan.-1900 June; 12397 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1900 July-1900 Dec.; 12396 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1902 Jan.-1902 June; 12395 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1902 July-1902 Dec.; 12394 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1905 Jan.-1905 June; 12393 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1905 July-1905 Dec.; 12392 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1906; 12391 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1906 Jan.-1906 June; 12390 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1906 July-1906 Dec.; 12389 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1907 Jan.-1908 Feb.; 12388 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1911 Feb.-1914 Oct.; 12387 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1916 Feb.; 12386 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1916 Mar.-1916 Nov.; 12385 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1918 Aug.-1918 Dec.; 12384 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1919 Jan.-1919 Mar.; 12383 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1919 April-1919 Dec.; 12382 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1920 Jan.-1920 June; 12381 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1920 July-1920 Dec.; 12380 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1921 Jan.-1921 June; 12379 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1921 July-1921 Dec.; 12378 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1922 Jan.-1922 June; 12377 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1922 July-1922 Dec.; 12376 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1923 Jan.-1923 June; 12375 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1923 July-1923 Dec.; 12374 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1924 Jan.-1924 June; 12373 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1924 July-1924 Dec.; 12372 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1925 Jan.-1925 June; 12371 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1925 July-1925 Dec.; 12370 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1926 Jan.-1927 May; 12369 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1931 April-1931 Aug.; 12368 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1931 Sept.-1931 Dec.; 12367 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1932 Jan.-1932 April; 12366 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1932 May-1932 Aug.; 12365 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1932 Sept.-1932 Dec.; 12364 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1933 Jan.-1933 Apr.; 12363 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1933 May-1933 Aug.; 12362 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1933 Sept.-1933 Dec.; 12361 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1934 Jan.-1934 Apr.; 12360 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1934 May-1934 Aug.; 12359 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1934 Sept.-1934 Nov.; 12358 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1935 Jan.-1935 July; 12357 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1935 Sept.-1936 Aug.; 12356 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1936 Dec.-1937 Spring; 12355 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1937 Summer-1937 Oct.; 12354 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1937 Dec.-1938 Mar.; 12353 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1938 Oct.-1939 Apr.; 12352 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1939 June-1939 Oct.; 12351 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1940; 12350 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Letters and Drafts of Articles Sent to Seventh Regiment Gazette, Never Published, undated; 12349 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Letters and Drafts of Articles Sent to Seventh Regiment Gazette, Never Published, 1937-1943; 12348 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Index for Cuts for Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1937; 12347 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Illustrations from the Seventh Regiment Gazette, Undated; 12346 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Illustrations from the Seventh Regiment Gazette, Undated; 12345 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Illustrations from the Seventh Regiment Gazette, Undated; 12344 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Illustrations from the Seventh Regiment Gazette, Undated; 12343 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Illustrations and Photographs from the Seventh Regiment Gazette, Undated; 12342 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Letter re Seventh Regiment Gazette, [1889 Dec.]; 12341 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re Seventh Regiment Gazette, Subscriptions and Business, 1931-1940; 12340 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Financial Statements re Seventh Regiment Gazette, 1932-1940; 12339 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette Letterhead, Undated; 12338 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette Subscription Cards, Undated; 12337 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re Seventh Regiment Guardsman, Subscriptions and Business, 1942-1946; 12336 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Financial Statements re Seventh Regiment Guardsman, 1941-1947; 12335 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Forms and Rates for Advertising in Seventh Regiment Guardsman, Undated; 12334 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Seventh Regiment Guardsman Subscription Cards, Undated; 12333 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - List of Subscribers, Publication Unclear, Undated; 12332 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Financial Statements, Publication Unclear, 1937-1939; 12331 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Financial Statements, Publication Unclear, 1938-1940; 12330 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence re general Publications, 1880, 1944; 12329 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Application for the Examination Prior to Export of Certain Designated Publications, [1940]; 12328 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Letters and Articles for Publications, Unclear if Used, 1939-1946; 12327 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette Subscription Cards, [1930]; 12326 (Box 54)
    - Seventh Regiment Guardsman, 1941-1946; 12325 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment Field Gazette, 1941; 12324 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Camp Worth Journal, 1855; 12323 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, Proofs, Illustrations, and other Publication Material, Undated; 12322 (Box 58)
    - The Merritt Dispatch, the Official Military Organ of Camp Merritt, 1919 Jan.-1919 Aug.; 12321 (Box 59)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette Vol. I-Vol. XXIV, 1886-1910; 12320 (Volume 386)
    - Seventh Regiment Gazette, Colonel Appleton Number, Vol. 30, No. 5, 1916 Feb.; 12319 (Volume 387)
    - Minute Book, Seventh Regiment Gazette Association, 1887-1897; 12318 (Volume 388)
    - Minute Book, Seventh Regiment Gazette Association, 1923-1927; 12317 (Volume 389)
    - Account Book, Seventh Regiment Guardsman, 1944-1946; 12316 (Volume 390)
    - The Knapsack, A Daily Journal of the Seventh Regiment New Armory Fair, 1879 Nov.-1879 Dec.; 12315 (Volume 391)
  - Subseries 2: Non-7th Regiment Publications, 12270
    This subseries contains publications and publication material that is not directly related to the 7th Regiment. Many of the publications are for a military audience. Most are arranged alphabetically.
    - Armed Forces Talk, 1951 Nov.-1952 Jan.; 12313 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Armed Forces Talk, 1952 Feb.-1952 Oct.; 12312 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Army Information Digest, 1951 Jan.-1951 Feb.; 12311 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - The Bugle, The Borderers' Chronicle, 1939 Mar., 1944 Dec.; 12310 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Coast Artillery Journal, 1948 May-1948 June; 12309 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - The East Lancashire Regimental Journal, The Essex Regiment Gazette, 1939 June, 1939 Sept.; 12308 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Firm: The Magazine of the Worcestershire Regiment, 1939 July; 12307 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - The Gallipoli Gazette, The Iron Duke, 1939 July, 1943 Feb.; 12306 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - The Journal of American History, 1916 Jan.-1916 Mar.; 12305 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - The Journal of the American History Foundation, The Journal of the United Service Institution of India, 1943 July, 1937 Spring; 12304 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - The Ladies World, 1875; 12303 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - The Light Bob Gazette, The Lion and the Rose, The London Scottish Regimental Gazette, 1939 Jan., 1946 Spring; 12302 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Military Review, 1947 May-1947 July; 12301 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Military Review, 1947 Aug.-1947 Oct.; 12300 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Military Review, 1947 Nov.-1947 Dec., 1948 Aug.; 12299 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Newsweek (International), 1976 July 4; 12298 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - The Park Avenue Social Review, 1932 May; 12297 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Post Bulletin, 1919 Aug.; 12296 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - The Ranger, 1939 May; 12295 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Report to the Army, 1952 Feb.-1952 Dec.; 12294 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - The Rio Grand Rattler (From Mexican Border Service), 1916; 12293 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - The Royal Dragon Guards Regimental Magazine, The Royal Military College of Canada, 1938 Dec.-1939 Mar.; 12292 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Scribner's Monthly, 1880-1881; 12291 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Sprig of Shillelagh (Journal of the Royal Innishilling Fusiliers), 1939 Summer; 12290 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - The Sunday Times Magazine, Time (International), July 1976; 12289 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - The X Royal Hussars Gazette, April 1939; 12288 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Army and Navy Journal, 1864-1865, 1889-1903; 12287 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - New York Times Mid-Week Pictorial, 1917 Feb.; 12286 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - The Saturday Evening Mail, 1914 Sept.-1915 May; 12285 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Army and Navy Illustrated, undated; 12284 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Rio Grande Rattler, 1916; 12283 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Washington Post, 1909; 12282 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1914-1915; 12281 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Puck, 1889; 12280 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Judge, 1889; 12279 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Harper's Weekly, 1881, 1883, 1886, 1889; 12278 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Frank Leslie's Illustrated, 1889; 12277 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - L'Illustration, 1921; 12276 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - The Bystander, 1916 May-1917 Nov.; 12275 (Volume 392)
    - The Countersign, 1893; 12274 (Volume 393)
    - Account Book/Subscription Book Republican Green Rifleman, 1811; 12273 (Volume 394)
    - The Trend, 1928 Mar.-1930 July; 12272 (Volume 395)
    - The Stars and Stripes, the Official Newspaper of the American Expeditionary Forces, 1918 Feb.8-1919 June 13; 12271 (Volume 396)
- Series XIV: Visual Materials, 1806-1983, 12104
  This series includes photographs, etchings, illustrations from periodicals, lantern slides, color prints, posters, negatives, and one daguerreotype.
  The bulk of photographs are individual portraits, company or other group portraits, scenes of activity in various camps (particularly Camp Smith in Peekskill, NY), marching units and parades, and interiors of the 7th Regiment Armory. There are portraits in albums and in boxes. Box 68 contains portraits of most all of the Regiment Colonels along with many others. This series also contains a number of Civil War portraits, both individual and group. The many camp photographs show members of the regiment involved in training activities of all kinds.
  Notable events are represented throughout the series. Examples include photographs of the Brooklyn Trolley Strike in 1895 (Box 61, Fol. 1), a photograph of the ticker tape parade for Charles Lindbergh in 1927 (Box 71, Fol. 6), and a photograph album entitled "Thirty-three War Time 1861-3 Photographs."
  Items of interest include color plates of military uniforms (1853-1858); French prints of charcoal and pencil sketches; "Life Studies of the Great Army" Etchings (1862-1865); and watercolor "Camp Sites at the Outbreak of the Civil War" (1862). A large extra illustrated volume completed in 1871 focuses on the 1861 participation of the 7th Regiment in the defense of Washington at the beginning of the Civil War.
  There are more than 115 posters in this series. Most involve recruitment and solicitation of financial support for World War I and represent the United States and several European countries. There are also a few depicting Civil War battles.
  - Portions of Personal Collections, 1895-1921, undated, 12265
    - John F. Daniell Includes photos of Brooklyn Trolley Strike (1895), 1883-1899; 12268 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - [G.D. Pitman]--Contents of Scrapbook, Photos, 1892-1896, undated; 12267 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Pages with Photographs, 1920-1921, undated; 12266 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Robert Lester--Photographs, 12254
    - Field Problem (Bush Hill, Westchester County, NY), 1942 Aug. 30; 12264 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Governor Lehman Speech at Kingsbridge Armory, 1942 Dec. 20; 12263 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1942 Sept. 23-Oct. 1; 12262 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1943 Aug. 15-24; 12261 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1943 Aug. 15-24; 12260 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - US Army, Second Service Command, Tactical School, Hackettstown, NJ, 1943 Oct. 24-30; 12259 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1944 Aug. 19-30; 12258 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1944 Aug. 19-30; 12257 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1944 Aug. 19-30; 12256 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Camp Smith, Peekskill, NY, 1945 Aug. 11-22; 12255 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - State Encampment at Peekskill, 1883, 12248
    - State Encampment, Peekskill, 1883; 12253 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - State Encampment, Peekskill, 1883; 12252 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - State Encampment, Peekskill, 1883; 12251 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - State Encampment, Peekskill, 1883; 12250 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - State Encampment, Peekskill, 1883; 12249 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Panoramic Views, 1893-1917, 12238
    - Zurich, 1893; 12247 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - 7th Regiment, Peekskill Camp, 1911 June; 12246 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - First Brigade NYNG Camp at Orange, Connecticut Maneuver Campaign, 1912 Aug. 10-19; 12245 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - West Point Parade Ground, 1914; 12244 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - McAllen, Texas, 1916 Aug. 8; 12243 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - McAllen, Texas, 1916 Sept. 6; 12242 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - McAllen, Texas, 1916; 12241 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - Madero, Texas, 1916; 12240 (Oversize Large [NS12])
    - Camp Wadsworth, Spartanburg, SC, 1917; 12239 (Oversize Large [NS12])
  - 7th Regiment Gazette and Guardsman Negatives, [1939]-1941, undated, 12236
    - Gazette and Guardsman Negatives, [1939]-1941, undated; 12237 (Box 65)
  - 7th Regiment Gazette and Guardsman Photographs, [1916]-[1947], 12222
    - Group Photograph in Camp, [1916]; 12235 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Fifth Regiment of Baltimore, 1935; 12234 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Instruction in Operation of Anti-Aircraft Gun, 1940; 12233 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Photos from the Second Quarter, 1940; 12232 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Photos from Second Quarter, 1940; 12231 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Marching Units, 1941, undated; 12230 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Marching Units, 1941-1942, undated; 12229 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Company Photographs, 1942-1946; 12228 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - "Mr. Westerman E Company", Undated; 12227 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - 7th Regiment War Memorial, Undated; 12226 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Oversize, Including Cover Photos, Undated; 12225 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Other Photos that Appeared in the Gazette/Guardsman, 1938-1942; 12224 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Other Photos that Appeared in the Gazette/Guardsman, 1938-[1947]; 12223 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - State Camp, Peekskill, NY--Loose Photographs, 12216
    - State Camp, Peekskill, NY, [1880-1890]; 12221 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - State Camp, Peekskill, NY, 1891-1895; 12220 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - State Camp, Peekskill, NY, 1895-1897; 12219 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - State Camp, Peekskill, NY, 1900-1910; 12218 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - State Camp, Peekskill, NY, [1930-1932], undated; 12217 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Portraits--Loose Photographs, 12211
    - Portraits, [1858]-[1915]; 12215 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 7th Regiment Colonels, Wetmore - Appleton, Undated; 12214 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 7th Regiment Colonels, Fisk - Tobin, 1930, undated; 12213 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - William C. Fisk, Undated; 12212 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 7th Regiment Armory--Interior Views, 12206
    - Seventh Regiment Armory Illustrated, The Decorator and Furnisher Magazine, Undated; 12210 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Armory--Interior Views, 1879-[1881], undated; 12209 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Armory--Interior Views, Company Rooms, [1880]; 12208 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Armory--Interior Views, Rooms, [1880-1881], undated; 12207 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 7th Regiment Armory, 12204
    - Notebook of photographs, clippings, ephemera, 1951-1983, undated; 12205 (Box 70)
  - Visual Materials, Various, 12187
    - Civil War (bulk photographs), 1861-1862, undated; 12203 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Astor Place Riots (clippings, illustrated), 1863; 12202 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Trolley Strike (photographs), 1895; 12201 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Col. Appleton (photographs), 1897-1916, undated; 12200 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Social Events (photographs), 1903-[1940]; 12199 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Parades (photographs), 1917, 1927, undated; 12198 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Killed in Action (photographs), [1917]-1923, undated; 12197 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Other Regiment Photographs and Illustrations, 1876-1962, undated; 12196 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Negatives, 1941, 1967, undated; 12195 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Stereoscopic Photos, 1877, undated; 12194 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Postcards--150th Anniversary, 1909, 1956; 12193 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Military Prints and Associated Correspondence, 1909, undated; 12192 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Dinner Place Card, 1913; 12191 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Armory, Illustrations, Undated; 12190 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Portraits--from 7th Regiment Song Book ("Songs of the 7th"), 1872, undated; 12189 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Fragments, 1862-1921, undated; 12188 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Visual Materials--Oversize, 12180
    - Illustration - Marching to Pennsylvania RR Depot, 1861; 12186 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Souvenir - Fort Washington, PA, 1875; 12185 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Trophies Won by Company F, 1892-1893; 12184 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 8th Co. Dramatic Assn., 1893; 12183 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 7th Regiment Mess Jacket, 1935; 12182 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - "Regimental Types at Creedmoor", Undated; 12181 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Visual Materials--Oversize, 12175
    - 7th Regiment in Camp Illustrations, 1883, 1887; 12179 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Military Sketches by D.W.C. Falls, 1820-1897; 12178 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 7th Regiment in Washington, 1858, 1893; 12177 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - WWI Illustrations, 1917-1918; 12176 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Visual Materials--Oversize, 12164
    - Drawing of Insignia, Undated; 12174 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Illustration--Review of Troops, Staten Island, 1860; 12173 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Illustration--Parade, Broadway, Undated; 12172 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Anniversary Celebration of Departure of Regiment for Washington, 1861 (photographs), 1911; 12171 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Recruitment Poster, Undated; 12170 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Walter Gresham Andrews, Wounded in Action, Undated; 12169 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Parade (photograph), Undated; 12168 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Camp Smith (photograph), 1927; 12167 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Camp Smith (photographs), 1930; 12166 (Box 74, Folder 9)